cmjuniversity.edu.in 2013-10-29

# Official Website - CMJ University, CMJ University Shillong, CMJ University Meghalaya, CMJ University Programs, MBA, CMJ University Courses

CMJ University acknowledges and respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our web site without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

**Information Collection**  
Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests, other information when needed to provide a service you requested. We do not collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our web site you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our web site.

When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. The provision of this information is voluntary but if information is not provided, the UMT may be unable to process your details for the purpose for which they were intended. You have a right of access to, and alteration of personal information concerning yourself.

We will always give you the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by clicking or checking the appropriate option or box at the point of collection. In some cases, when applicable, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in." This means we will require your affirmative action to indicate your consent before we use your information for purpose for which it was submitted.

**How We Use the Information Collected**  
CMJ University uses the information collected for several general purposes: to process your application, registration or enquiry for an CMJ University activity or interest group; to keep you up-to-date on the latest product announcements, upcoming events or other information we think you would like to hear about; and to understand your needs better and provide you with better services.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
As a general rule, your personal information is never shared outside CMJ University or disclosed to a third party without the individual's consent. CMJ University may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: when we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested, or when we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of CMJ University to provide a product or service to you (We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service. They are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose). We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our web sites.

**Third Party Sites**  
CMJ University web site contains links to other sites. CMJ University does not share your personal information with those web sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
CMJ University may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this page.
